In this video, I will share with you the results of our current digital technology, intelligent technology, and fashion innovation combined with the results of the fashion designers, scholars, experts, and researchers.
I will mainly share from two aspects.
The first is the demand for modern lifestyle and fashion industry development.
The second is the demand for digital technology and fashion design innovation.
The demand for modern lifestyle and fashion industry development is mainly based on three aspects.
The first is the trend of modern cultural background and fashion style.
The second is the new foundation of digital infrastructure and fashion innovation.
The third is how digitalization can improve the efficiency of fashion design.
Modern cultural background.
The third is the demand for economic development to meet the needs of our future material culture, agriculture, and industrial information civilization.
The third is the globalized vision under the background of big data.
The fourth is the digitalization of intelligent information culture, fashion, fashion, and fashion.
The rapid development of digital technology provides a new development environment for fashion industry design.
In fact, it also leads to the digitalization of our modern life.
This is already very obvious.
Everyone knows that we can't live without computers and mobile phones.
Our shopping, consumption, entertainment, etc.
are all around digitalization.
In this context, we need to study the direction of our modern lifestyle.
Beijing recently released a new lifestyle.
There are all kinds of lifestyle.
For example, home-cultivation, spiritual practice, traveling, doing strange things, retrograde, and so on.
These are all some of the changes in our modern lifestyle under digitalization and informationization.
I summarized it in four aspects.
The most basic is to meet the needs of physical function to improve the level of ecological health.
Why do we need to level up?
To meet the basic needs of the physical body.
But now we have entered a height of pursuing big health and ecological health.
The second is to meet the needs of social function.
The need to diversify the society under the need of social function.
The need to diversify our society now.
We are no longer satisfied with the basic needs of material, social life, etc.
We are no longer satisfied with the basic needs of social life and ecological health.
We need to meet more social and safety needs.
We need to meet the individualization of the lifestyle that respects the self-demanding function.
You can now see the individualized customized services in digital society.
There are various individualized
The most important is to achieve the artistic preservation of the self-value and mental need.
The revival of our current culture and the reformation of our culture
I will briefly talk about this.
The transformation of lifestyle drives the three changes in the fashion industry such as digitalization and digitalization.
The main focus is on the transformation from the focus to the distribution, from the group to the personality, and from the market to the customer.
Again, why do we need to make such a change?
In our country's various policies, there is good strategic leadership.
We have received national recognition in the digital technology system from the plan of 14.5 and the original plan of 2035.
The industrialization and digitalization of digital negative energy and intelligent design has become the current direction of development.
Mainly, the Internet, artificial intelligence, big data, virtual reality, and smart manufacturing, industrial Internet,
have provided strong conditions for the transformation from fashion industry to manufacturing.
In addition, the digital technology has also been developed.
In the fashion industry, the application of Claude is relatively popular in Europe and the United States,
especially in some major fashion and fashion brands.
How to better meet the fashion needs of the new life style?
How can digital and cultural innovation, content production and security,
combine with various industries to cross-border Internet?
The practical, real-life, and future intelligent design
fashion, digital industry development and the development of fashion and technology design.
We are now in the teaching of our fashion academy.
A lot of digital rich people
So our school has also established a digital fashion design research center
To build a digital fashion brand
The digitalization of fashion products is mainly in four aspects
Digitalization of resources
Digitalization of production management
Digitalization of operation management
And the digitalization of quality control in four aspects
Now the cloud software has been able to penetrate the whole of fashion
From inspiration to investigation to final operation management
Digitalization of quality control in all aspects
Now we already have a certain brand
Be able to carry out digitalized design applications and management in a full process
Even some Google tracking in the back
In fact, the intelligentization of fashion design production
Mainly one of the materials
Human resources
Financial supply
Design of supply and supply production control
In the process of design production
The foundation of the business is in the trend prediction
I particularly emphasize the design perspective
Trend prediction
So technology supply
Data information of business management and customer information
Rely on many of this business management systems
ERPR
OAS system
MES system
AI trend prediction system
Realize data fusion and high-resolution virtual imaging
Constructing six intelligent big data platforms
Different traditional design production
Different verification
So now they are all unified in a platform
In our Hangzhou
Many small and medium-sized clothing companies
Have been using such a process in a large number of ways
Especially in the use of foreign trade
In this epidemic
The communication between these three countries and foreign trade companies
All realized
Provide convenience and efficiency for fashion design
The usual operation of our clothing brand process
Mainly research and development projects and projects
From the collection of pieces of fabric to the final production
From the collection of inspiration
We learn to design
Everyone knows
The positioning of the crowd
Whether it's from the young middle to the big
There are also some fashion senses
How do we go from age
From this market
Fashion availability
And so on
Different perspectives for research and development
Traditional research used to rely on manpower
Now it is often dependent on data
The selection of products and details
Also our traditional research and development
Even there are interviews
There are design designs
Designs of all kinds of patterns and patterns
The determination of the fabric
There are also custom designs
It's a coat, a coat, a skirt, a skirt
Or pants, skirt, top and bottom
How to determine
So the regular design process
Everyone sees waste time waste work
The cost of communication is very high
And the process is relatively long
From the collection, review, repair, sample, review, repair, order meeting
We repeat it again and again
It's a process
Digital rich fashion design
Is to use some
A.I. design and A.I. popular trend prediction
Can follow certain rules and principles
From the whole network to quickly collect
Related pictures and documents
And combine business brand positioning and historical sales data
Then on the pattern design
You can also use digital methods
Search for all the theme materials
Then the key words given by the designer
The more the more accurate
Then we can also use digital intelligence software
Perform
Individual elements of creation
Expand the composition of the creative combination
I will give you some examples later
For the second process
Is communication and sampling
So fashion design
Intellectualization is mainly reflected in 3D design software
Virtual reality test platform
And other diversified data and information channels
Online design through 3D
Most designers today
Still use flat design software
Then 3D design can be through
The fabric is almost 100% virtual
From texture to color
From material to texture
All can be
Fulfilled in the process of sampling
High-definition virtual mapping
Then we are still on the platform for modeling and plating
Adjusting in trial
Now many companies have done it on the platform
Do electronic samples
Electronic craft
Including every seam line
Its distance
Its fabric is almost all through virtual mapping
Methods to achieve
Customers can see it on this platform
Share
The second part is the digital technology industry
Fashion design innovation
First of all, the first is the interaction between images and design and production
The first is based on visual image production
Especially applied in our creative design field
What I just said is the entire process of our fashion industry
In fact, in the process of our innovation
Digital technology with our innovation
Image innovation
And some design innovation
How to integrate
Image is the most current
By establishing a combination of machine vision and artificial intelligence
Automatically integrate innovation and innovation
Image design
For example, now we can enter a small shark swimming in the lake
In the model of a motorcycle
Electric board made of three-dimensional
The combination of the lion and the turtle, etc.
Then in the artificial intelligence system
It will
Based on the language you input
Create a new image
But currently in the AI system
And our current
In the chat system
How to ensure original
There is a moral and moral issue
In the creative process, it is very particular about original creation
So in this
There is an original database
The content of the composition is inside
How do we
Create a basic database for original creation
A lot of innovation still needs to be through our usual
Original or normal
The accumulation of this pattern
And the accumulation of design elements
The second is based on three-dimensional software
Pattern, division, division
The pattern is re-created
Then you can use division art
Dividing art is actually a kind of production art
It is a kind of algorithmic art form
Expansion algorithm
It is using computers and mathematics
Produce anti-reference symmetrical pattern design
Then
In the creation of art rendering software
Mander, Sandy, these software are all based on pattern
A software for pattern division
It can set the formula here
Adjust parameters
Create
Creative patterns of different art styles
I want to emphasize
Through division art
The previous pattern of it
I still want to emphasize the original creation
Emphasize this intellectual property
Can't use
Other things to do analysis
Then it still has
Intellectual property risk
Because now many artists
Some are relatively substandard
Use software to create
I think this is not art
But the development of technology is
Irreplaceable
Future technology
It is still for us
Social life for our production
Serve our way of life
Technology development can be effective
For us
To better
Create more art works and art forms
The third is the automatic production of parameters guided by parameters
Using the online tools and programs such as everypile
Based on the pre-designed rich texture pattern library
Designers can choose the pattern they like to carry out
Multi-parameter adjustment
Then adjust the size, density and color of the elements in this
Can generate
Some unique personality
The pattern
In short
The pattern you predicted
It all has to have a cool presence
This is a lot of software
The production of a lot of databases
Including some enterprises
He is doing it himself
This database
Because in order to protect his intellectual property
The fourth is the digital pattern composition and design
This digital pattern composition design
MiHui smart flower platform
There is a MiHui smart flower platform in the Jiangzhe area
It has a lot of patterns in it
He combined with
The flower-shaped sales mall
The flower-shaped online smart design
The flower-shaped customized development
Comprehensive platform
Through artificial intelligence technology
Actual collection analysis market
The popular flower-shaped design program
Hold and predict the trend
Automatically make patterns and composition
Creative design of other aspects
Of course there must be
Relative input
Relative settings
Can generate rich patterns
And for color
Automatic analysis and color
Color data information
Through multiple link development
Color
Digitalized and visualized
Smart transmission management system
Through some smart eyes
Multi-lens image color measurement system
Realize
A small copy of the four products
Automatically color
Manufactured
Smart formula
Color
Color color system
Also achieved
Digitalization
Industrial production
Automatic color
Using Kroma
Automatic color software
Artificial intelligence
There is a teacher in our team
He specifically
From traditional clothing
Take different colors on top
Use the standard of the combination of traditional clothing
Automatically color in the application software
Form a rich
Classic color color scheme
This article just
Get a second area of ​​SCI
The third is the image color system
Based on the image color of Petal
Supplemental and superimposition functions
By modeling the construction of the image
Automatically identify the scene
Analysis
Provide different color schemes
In this system
Color matching
It is very rich
It will be based on
Automatic identification of different shapes
The third is the texture
Fashion presents a new scene
The first is the use of new materials
In the original material designed by fashion
Not only
Increase the development of new materials
For example
With technology-adjusted fashion products
To create a green technology ecosystem
Under the promotion of the theme of the original universe
Use ultra-high-precision 3D digital fabric simulation technology
As I just said
On the fabric
Real data collection
Now
Many of our software already has a large number of
Fabric database
When we are designing
These high-precision fabric
Data in
The library
When we are designing at any time
Can use these digital fabrics
Through AI physics engine implementation
To virtualize this fabric
The previous fabric is pure
The pattern is made
Now it's almost the same
You see it
With real material
It's exactly the same
The second is the new scene of the original universe
The arrival of the virtual era
Fashion fashion has gone digital
Is inevitable
We now have
Digital models
Multicultural new scene
Then the virtual technology and fashion must be perfectly integrated
I was thinking about our school's digital show this year
On a wave bridge
This wave bridge is the surface of the water
Our wave bridge is the real show on the wave bridge
The T-shaped extension data below the wave bridge
Is on our lake
We are working on the design of the plan
If we succeed
We will integrate the real show with the virtual show
And in
Change in different
Scenes and spaces
After the epidemic
Our graduation show
Will be very bright
Also welcome everyone to pay attention
The fourth is the sense
It's about style
Style identification
In the end, our design still needs to show a style
The first one is that we can do it through
Automatic replacement through smart software
On the Internet
Very convenient
Various smart switches
The second is the array design
Through the use of store array focus objective analysis
In the virtual space
Where are our eyes looking
Where is our scene
The third is the style identification
The creative clothing style has a demonstration platform
By clothing
The fabric style is a detailed capture
Analysis of the style of positioning clothing
Therefore, emotional evaluation
Because for
Style identification
Through intelligence
Can effectively locate our design
Then our team
What did you do
In terms of digitalization
Then the first one
Our team is in the panoramic virtual interaction technology support
Digitalization of Chinese traditional silk
We start from the material of traditional silk
Color decoration process and physical chemistry information
Collect our traditional silk food and raw material for digitalization processing
In the form of 3D to show
Our Chinese silk
The characteristics of Chinese silk clothing
For fashion design
Provide the information library of traditional clothing art resources
And this digitalization we are doing
Triangular display
Virtual imitation
This one we
Last year
Put online
Showed for a while
The second is virtual imitation technology to achieve information technology and design innovation practice
We combine our Zhijiang University of Technology
Fashion design national level
Virtual imitation
Experimental center
Silk culture
Passed on to product design digitalization technology
The main laboratory of the cultural department
Use the PC section and clothing brand of the retail terminal
Design online platform and other virtual
Interferential platform
In the knowledge of virtual experimental equipment and spare experimental materials
Students in the simulation scene
Perform traditional clothing observation
Through digitalization of digital design
Increase students' understanding of traditional clothing and fashion design
We are on this platform
Our students are wearing
Related to
Virtual imitation
This teaching event
At the same time we are
When we are doing social service
We are trying to do something
The first
We have a
Bo
Chuanxiguan
Collected a lot of traditional clothing
There are a lot of traditional clothing on a large number of traditional clothing
Then we have to take these cultural items
And carry out related drafts
Drafting
This is our original pattern
Under the supervision of our team
This is self-developed
Traditional cultural items
For the collection of stock prices
From which it was mass-produced drafts
And into
In the drawing software
Second creation
I just said that the database of basic patterns
If we go through our own creation
May take a long time to accumulate
And the application of digital software
For our patterns to extract drafts and mass-produce
For the second creation and the third creation for the division and structure of patterns
Provided good support
We are in
With the support of the software we developed by ourselves
Our basic pattern of drafts
Has reached a rapid growth
It took us nearly a year from last year to now
Now basically all the curves have been done
Can be closed
And continuous
But still further optimization
This is what we extract from traditional clothing
Then use digital software
To extract
Deep mass-produced drafts
We are taking these to carry out secondary creation
Combination of art
This can guarantee
The intellectual property of our patterns
Then this is the digital pattern
Then we use
Pattern monster software
Change its shape size
Pattern color change
A process
The second is
Patterns generated by mathematical algorithms
Will also generate a large number of
Strange or creative
There are individual patterns
The third is through the nervous system
The software generated by stylized images
We generate various AI through language description
This is the change and transition of styles
Then generate
Different
Patterns and images
This is a lot of software, everyone knows
Drawing and painting software
In our design
There are still more applications
The most important thing we are now developing by ourselves
These
AI auxiliary design systems
The fourth is the MiHui software
MiHui software is in the shape creation
Now it is relatively mature
Then it has a free arrangement of single elements
The elements and background colors are
Various free switches
Then as long as your basic patterns are more
Can generate a large number of
New patterns
Of course this can be created with themes
This is where we are every day
At least through
Mathematical means
Can produce
Dozens of standardized
Businessable
Pattern pattern
The third aspect is diversification of numbers
Of the Chinese media platform
Promote traditional vibrational memory and culture
This is based on AI and VR
Predictable virtual verbal
It is a digital virtual reality
To strengthen reality technology
To do live shows or language video connection
Promotes the traditional vibrational
Memory culture
Then this is what we
For transmission
We do the traditional
There are some stories behind ourilli
Promote and transmission
The fourth is virtual chip technology implementation
Information technology and design innovation
We are now using the three-dimensional human body measuring chair,
clothing male and female,
plant style chair,
three-dimensional virtual test platform,
as well as some testing systems and equipment
to carry out the experiment of digitalization of clothing engineering,
human body engineering,
and the comfort of new fabric design.
Smart design provides practical environment and conditions,
because we have two such laboratories in our school.
The relationship between our clothing,
human body engineering,
and three-dimensional fabric,
we carry out relevant data experiments.
In the future, we will also use information-based methods
to achieve such experiments,
to be more forward-looking,
more technological.
The fifth is smart visualization technology software
to promote analysis of fashion development and trends.
Everyone should be using this more widely now.
That is to say, we use smart software
to analyze the current market,
all types of markets,
to be able to accurately predict the future of fashion development and trends.
We can also use this kind of mathematical analysis
to broaden the scope of anti-fashion clothing
and cultural human knowledge and social issues,
to provide research methods for the development of future literature and new literature.
At present, analysis of fashion market trends in the United States
is basically based on the data analysis of smart software
and the basis of case analysis.
The University of Louisiana,
the University of Louisiana,
where they are engaged in related research,
is based on such a basis.
Finally, to summarize,
the characteristics of digital fashion,
one is the diversity of fashion.
Digital fashion is defined as the intersection of the digital world.
It is a variety of subjects,
including the imitation of biomechanical machinery,
design, computer, information technology, etc.
The second is the democratization of fashion personality.
The equipment that can be worn now
is still in its early stages.
I believe that in our imitation fiber,
its intelligent function identification aspect,
function protection aspect,
protection aspect,
and fabric perception aspect
will do better and better.
More and more,
it can serve our human ecological health
and information transmission.
The third is fashion ecology.
The fourth is digital coalescence.
Digital technology and artificial intelligence coalesce and coagulate.
It presents such a characteristic that I have in me.
This is the four characteristics of future digital fashion.
I will briefly introduce
our work related to digital intelligence.
Please give your comments and suggestions.
Thank you.